Guide to the Cornell University Treasurer's Office records,1876-1955.
Cornell University Treasurer's Office records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Treasurer's Office records, 1876-1955.
7-6-86
Cornell University.Treasurer's Office.
35.6 cubic feet; 248 volumes.
Vouchers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Legal files, credit books, cash books, vouchers, fund reports, contracts, bids, and many other financial records of the University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Legal files, credit books, cash books, vouchers, fund reports, contracts, bids, and many other financial records of the University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Finances.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the Office of Origin.
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #7-1-1610, 7-7-1636, 7-1-1345, 7-6-86, 7-6-425, 7-6-13, and 7-6-1110.
CONTAINER LIST
- W.H. Woodward - Vouchers, 1868; 1869 (Box 1)
- E.G. Putman - Vouchers, 1869-1871 (Box 1)
- Vouchers, Sept. 1871-Dec. 1871 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous letters and administrative information (Box 1)
- Alphabetized Vouchers, 1871-1875 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1872 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1873 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1874 (Box 2)
- Vouchers, 1875 (Box 3)
- Vouchers, 1876 (Box 3)
- Vouchers, 1877 (Box 3)
- Vouchers, 1878 (Box 3)
- Vouchers, 1879 (Box 3)
- Miscellaneous Vouchers, 1877-1880 (Box 3)
- Vouchers, Mar. 1880-Dec. 1880 (Box 4)
- Vouchers, 1881 (Box 4)
- Vouchers, Jan. 1882-July 1882 (Box 4)
- Vouchers Mics., 1873-1877 (Box 4)
- Vouchers Misc., 1880-1881 (Box 4)
- Vouchers, Aug. 1882-Dec. 1882 (Box 5)
- Vouchers, 1883 (Box 5)
- Vouchers, Jan. 1884-Aug. 1884 (Box 5)
- Vouchers, SEpt. 1884-Dec. 1884 (Box 6)
- Vouchers, 1885 (Box 6)
- Vouchers, Jan. 1886-Nov. 1886 (Box 6)
- Vouchers, Dec. 1886 (Box 7)
- Vouchers, 1887 (Box 7)
- Vouchers (except June), 1888 (Box 7)
- Cornell University Medical College, 1901-1906 (Box 7)
- Miscellaneous, 1905-1906 (Box 7)
- Vouchers, 1922 (Box 8)